## Jeffrey W. Jarvis

jeffrey.jarvis32@gmail.com • M: 678.602.2673 • LinkedIn

## **CAREER SUMMARY:**

Aspiring sales professional with +3 years' experience working complex sales cycles with C-Level Executives. Passionate about driving revenue in exciting growth environments. Ability to build strong relationships navigating sales cycles with key decision makers at all levels of client organizations.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Izenda Inc. Atlanta, GA
Account Executive June 2017 - Present

- Achieved quarterly quotas goals in the **first 6 months**
- Navigated highly technical sales cycles working with all aspects of prospecting accounts including executive management, developer teams, and product teams
- Led sales team strategy training sessions to implement past sale experience with new hires
- Led sales analysis and forecasting for 100s of accounts and prospects reducing sales cycle time
- Worked directly with Izenda CEO implementing strategies designed to boost sales acumen and speed to sale

Gartner Inc. Fort Myers, FL
Account Manager Jan 2016 – May 2017

- Enhanced and managed a book of business increasing revenue by 50% in a year. Saved \$250,000 of risky renewals
- Prospected new customers through cold calling, email communications, social media networking, and in person meetings Achieved 156% of quota in nine months
- Developed relationships with current clients driving added ROI via ongoing consultative engagements providing strategic direction and innovative insights resulting in an average of 25% YoY Revenue Growth
- Trained and certified in ValueSelling

Youth Today – Center for Sustainable Journalism

**Circulation/Advertising Sales Associate** 

Kennesaw, GA Feb 2014 – Jan 2015

- Drove sales for Youth Today Publication employing best practice cold calling and email communications, consistently exceeded monthly quotas by over 25%
- Selected for Promotion to Advertising Sales in the first six months due to sales merit and leadership potential
- Acted as subject matter expert and in-house trainer for new employee onboarding and sales techniques
- Ranked as top monthly individual contributor in sales force on multiple occasions

AquaTots Swim Schools

Kennesaw, GA June 2011 – Dec 2015

- **Aquatics Director** 
  - Earned multiple promotions to eventually land in the local franchise director role
     Formed and managed a team of 16 swim instructors including staffing, training, and creating lesson plans
  - Providing the highest level of customer service for any parent with concerns or questions about the classes or lesson plans resulting in upselling 30% of the problem accounts
  - Developing sales strategies to drive revenue during slow seasons

**EDUCATION:** 

Kennesaw State University Bachelor of Business Administration, Professional Sales Kennesaw, GA Dec 2015